A day ahead of the contentious US election
outcome, our markets managed to remain
comfortable in the green with gains coming in
across the board and that was riding on the
back of pretty healthy cues coming in
from across the globe so we ended the
trading day higher by 144 points on the
Nifty at
1181 for the Sensex as well we held out
through out the trading day and wrapped up 500
points higher at
4261 while the mid cap index did manage
to see a bit of a fall but the small cap index did quite a bit
and by the time we
slipped up you did see it come from the top of
the day the Nifty Bank continued to remain a
solid out performer in trade today and you also had
support coming in from the likes
of auto, metals, pharma, PSU banks that did
manage to gain traction on the flip
side, real estate lost out on energy.
Well as media they were in the red let's take it then
straight to the top Nifty gainers and
trade today ICICI Bank in the green
Indalco SBI hdfcfund.com
extraordinary beat that you saw on
the profit front as well they was all quite
healthy and the stock due
rally Godrej Properties came out with
earnings revenue at about 14 crore and 4
crore and that was very encouraging a pardon me that was
Deepak Fertilizers
with an encouraging set of numbers a Godrej
Properties was having disappointing profits
doodling to just about 7 crore versus 32
crore or else Beverages another result candid pat ed
about 161 crore revenue at
1839 crore you had mouth finance which came out
with its numbers NII growth pat both continue to
remain rad healthy and as I
said Deepak  Fertilizers
quite a decent set of numbers double as well came
out with its numbers a 482 crore pat
and that certainly surpassed the expectations
you had revenue growth as well that was quite
steady j ad steel another earnings
candidate 356 crore pat and you had something like
Cannes Nerolac as well that came out with its
numbers w in the broader universe an
just identification
infrastructure dhani green two and some of the
losers come tomorrow all are going to be on
the US elections and we've got a slew of
experts joining in to discuss the big
event